[EPIC]⚡ Ladies and gentlemen, you've heard all the evidence.
[EPIC]⚡ I submit that this was not a hot -blooded crime of passion.
[EPIC]⚡ Consider this, a revolver holds six bullets, not eight.
[EPIC]⚡ That means that he fired the gun empty and then stopped to
[EPIC]⚡ reload.
[EPIC]⚡ By the power vested in me by the state of Maine,
[EPIC]⚡ I hereby order you to serve two life sentences back to back.
[EPIC]⚡ One for each of your victims.
[EPIC]⚡ So be it.
[EPIC]⚡ Send you here for life, that's exactly what they take.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I believe in two things, discipline and the Bible.
[EPIC]⚡ Here you'll receive both.
[EPIC]⚡ Andy came to Shawshank prison in 1947.
[EPIC]⚡ Why'd you do it?
[EPIC]⚡ I didn't since you asked.
[EPIC]⚡ You can fit right in.
[EPIC]⚡ I must admit, I didn't think much of Andy first time I
[EPIC]⚡ laid eyes on him.
[EPIC]⚡ He had a quiet way about it, a walk, a talk that
[EPIC]⚡ just wasn't normal around here.
[EPIC]⚡ There are places in the world that aren't made out of stone.
[EPIC]⚡ There's something inside that they can't touch.
[EPIC]⚡ What are you talking about?
[EPIC]⚡ Hope.
[EPIC]⚡ Let me tell you something, my friend.
[EPIC]⚡ Hope is a dangerous thing.
[EPIC]⚡ Damn it, new friend, you're putting me behind.
[EPIC]⚡ You drive a man insane.
[EPIC]⚡ You better be sick or dead in there, I kid you not.
[EPIC]⚡ I better get used to that idea.
[EPIC]⚡ Oh my holy God.
[EPIC]⚡ As it comes down to a simple choice, you're gonna like busy
[EPIC]⚡ living or die.
[EPIC]⚡ Busy living or get busy dying.
[EPIC]⚡ Damn right.